letstalkpayments.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. Period. We live in your world too and we will never do anything with your information that we would not want to be done with ours. It’s that simple! Of course, there’s a longer version for you to review:

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to MEDICI or fill out any kind of form.

When subscribing or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously and obtain reduced benefits from the site.

MEDICI stores users Name and Email Address provided by user during registration for login credentials and access to services/products. All user data is provided by consent. Users are able to access the site without consent and login, but must provide consent for access to paid services/products/subscriptions.

Once the data has been registered with MEDICI, it is stored on servers managed by MEDICI’s server provider(s).

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience: your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

  * To improve our website: we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you

  * To process transactions: your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Your phone number may be used for confirming your identity and authenticating your login.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow in your settings, that enable the sites or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties, any of your personally identifiable payment-related information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential and secure. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Basic user profile information and company profile may be shared with our customers who have agreed to this Privacy Policy to gain access to the site features, products and services.

Your contact information will not be disclosed without your consent or explicit action during registration. Users on MEDICI can view your company profile and your user profile. If you follow an organization, you will be listed among its followers, which can be viewed by others including the page owner. We use aggregate information about followers and viewers to provide data about such pages’ performance (for example, visits and updates).

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Disclaimer**

Please also visit our Disclaimer section of the Terms of Use establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at gomedici.com/tos/.

**Your Consent**

If you are under the age of 13, you should ask your parent or guardian for assistance when using our site and you should not submit any personal information without their permission. You may not make any financial transactions on this site without the permission of your parent or guardian.

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us.
